vebra.com 2009-06-19

# Vebra.com plc - Privacy Policy

### Privacy policy

This Privacy Policy sets out the data processing practices carried out through the use of the Internet and the World Wide Web by Vebra plc. The vebra.com website is a comprehensive listing of detailed property particulars, and therefore, we want to help you find what you want as quickly and smoothly as possible. 

### Information collected

We collect personal information from visitors to this web site through the use of online forms. 

### Use of personal information

By providing you with the option of registering we can give you a quicker access to your favourite preferences, by allowing you to save searches. 

In addition, we provide a facility for you use our registration facility to forward your details to the relevant Estate Agency. If you are interested in viewing a property or want to contact the agency, add the property to your basket. When you are satisfied with your selection click on register in your property basket. When you register any details you provide will be sent to the Agents concerned. The information held when the user ticks 'Remember my details for future contact' can be edited when the client returns to the registration page. We may also use the information we collect to occasionally notify you about important functionality changes to the Web site, new services and special offers we think you'll find valuable. If you would rather not receive this information, please send an e-mail to [enquiries@vebra.com](mailto:enquiries@vebra.com). Make sure to change your preferences for each account or e-mail address you have left with us. 

### Use of cookies

You will need to enable cookies on your Web browser in order to access all features of vebra.com “Cookies” are a standard for storing small amounts of data on a web client (i.e. the web browser on your computer). Any web server (including the one that holds our web site) may store one or more cookies in your browser, or, request your browser to transmit certain data to the web server. We may store cookies on your web browser in order to enhance your visit to the website, because by using the cookies, we can track information about your usage of the site, provide customised content, or even the use of password protection. 

### Sale of business

In the event that our business is sold or integrated with another business your details may be disclosed to our advisors and any prospective purchasers’ advisers and they may be passed onto the new owners of the business. 

### Hyperlinks

Vebra.com contains links to third party Web sites and resources on the internet. Vebra.com provides links to these other Web sites only as a convenience. This privacy policy only covers the Vebra plc’s Website at [www.vebra.com](http://www.vebra.com/) their links within this site to other websites are not covered by this policy, so we urge you to be careful when you enter any personal information online. Vebra plc accepts no responsibility or liability for these sites. 

### Your consent

By using our Web site you consent to the collection and use of this information by Vebra plc. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it.
